Stanford University LGBT Alumni Oral History InterviewsLGBT Oral History Interviews SC1164
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University LGBT alumni oral history interviews
2011-2013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Davies, Andrea.
SC1164
20462.38 megabyte(s)
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audio and transcripts from oral histories conducted with LGBT Stanford alumni.
Transgender people -- United States -- Biography.; Bisexual college students -- United States.; Gay college students -- California.; Lesbian college students -- United States.; Davies, Andrea.
- Audio, 2011-2013
  - Andrews, Megan, 2012 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Austin, Steven, 2012 Aug 8; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Balasubramanian, Janani, 2013 Jun 12; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Bauer, Chris, 2013 May 2; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Brenner, Daniel, 2013 May 3; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Casscells, Anne, 2012 Jul 26; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Cirksena, Kathryn, 2013 Jun 3; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Crockett, Vivian, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Croonquist, Robert, 2012 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Elias, John, 2013 May 6; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Fabian, Angel, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Freed, John, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Garber, Linda, 2011 Jun 7; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Herman, Paul, 2012 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Johnson, Fenton, 2011 May 2; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Joseph, Miranda, 2012 Aug 9; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Kapadia, Ronak, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
    Access to Collection
    Accessible in the Special Collections Reading Room only.
  - Kaye, Steven, 2013 May 5; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Koskovich, Gerard, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Lane, Clayton, 2013 May 20; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Levinson, Kathy, 2013 Feb 27, Mar 6; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Liecty, Derek, 2011 Nov 16; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Maravilla, Carl, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Melton, Buck, 2013 May 29; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Morales, Sofia, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Naess, Raghar, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Nerman, Maud, 2013 Jun 2; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Nosanchuk, Matt, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Perez, Rosa, 2013 May 31; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Robinson, Paul, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Sanchez, Tony, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Starbird, Kate, 2013 May 10; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Stewart, James, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Vargas, Nicholas, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Wadden, Laura, 2012 Jul 231; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Yost, Don, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
  - Young, Katie, 2013 Jul 1; 1 computer file(s) (wav)
- Transcripts, 2011-2013
  - Andrews, Megan, 2012 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Balasubramanian, Janani, 2013 Jun 12; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Crockett, Vivian, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Croonquist, Robert, 2012 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted until 2022-05-22.
  - Elias, John, 2013 May 6; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Garber, Linda, 2011 Jun 7; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Johnson, Fenton, 2011 May 2; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Kapadia, Ronak, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (pdf)
  - Levinson, Kathy, 2013 Feb 27, Mar 6; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Morales, Sofia Lee, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Nosanchuk, Matt, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Robinson, Paul, 2013 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Starbird, Kate, 2013 May 10; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Stewart, James, 2011 May; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)
  - Wadden, Laura, 2012 Jul 23; 1 computer file(s) (PDF)